{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515688491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515688490"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 600cdc58-4db2-4b72-9cee-394cf453b1a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515689545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515689545"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 600cdc58-4db2-4b72-9cee-394cf453b1a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515692955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515692955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 600cdc58-4db2-4b72-9cee-394cf453b1a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515693120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515693120"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 600cdc58-4db2-4b72-9cee-394cf453b1a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515726236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515726236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" bb4f52b9-ae45-4d45-8a55-f0c245c4f16e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_mno-mwalimu-bado-mwenye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515744241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515744241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" bb4f52b9-ae45-4d45-8a55-f0c245c4f16e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_mno-bado-vya-wao"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515755336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515755336"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" bb4f52b9-ae45-4d45-8a55-f0c245c4f16e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mno_mno-bado-vya-wao"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515755409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515755409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" bb4f52b9-ae45-4d45-8a55-f0c245c4f16e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baisikeli yake ilikuwa fupi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515774688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515774688"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515776766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515776766"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515778839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515778839"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515781964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515781964"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515784156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515784156"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515786336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515786336"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515789101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515789101"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515791258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515791257"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515793410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515793410"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515794387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515794387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515794463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515794463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 9094be83-4e01-4a77-b816-32674bc5c8e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515805819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515805819"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515808201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515808201"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515810490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515810489"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515811780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515811780"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515814160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515814160"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515816942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515816942"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515819412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515819412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515826704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515826704"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515829062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515829062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515830401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515830401"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515832669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515832669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515834104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515834104"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515836404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515836404"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515837958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515837957"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515840416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515840416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515845398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515845398"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515847708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515847708"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515851393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515851393"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515853943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515853943"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515857633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515857633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515859649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515859649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515859801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515859801"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 13283671-1f07-4d85-9510-f75d81af3ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515871497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515871497"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515876732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515876731"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515878355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515878354"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAGIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515885886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515885886"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAGIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515887458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515887458"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FUPI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515895644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515895644"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FUPI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515897229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515897229"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FARASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515910185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515910185"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FARASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" START_FARASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515910422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515910421"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FARASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515913442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515913442"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515922237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515922237"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515924268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515924268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515924406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515924405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 66137eca-759e-40ee-87dd-319591460b9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515956764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515956764"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 723a4579-9f95-4c06-9a4f-bf437f29e009"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_ndege-pamoja-pale-jinsi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515977880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515977880"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 723a4579-9f95-4c06-9a4f-bf437f29e009"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ndege_ndege-pamoja-pale-jinsi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515977952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515977952"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 723a4579-9f95-4c06-9a4f-bf437f29e009"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515989755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515989754"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_G-O-F"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515993282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515993282"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_H-F-V"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548515998512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548515998512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_H-F-V"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516004802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516004802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-S-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516008737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516008737"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_M-F-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516014368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516014368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_M-F-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516020195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516020194"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_M-F-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516023288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516023288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_I-F-W"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516026381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516026381"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Y-J-F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516031698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516031698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Y-J-F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516035447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516035447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-V-I"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516038303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516038303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_W-F-M"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516043823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516043823"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_W-F-M"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516047002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516047001"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_A-T-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516053392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516053392"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_A-T-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516057242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516057242"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_181430"," gameId":" 03150d51-42de-4224-8494-f1ea1f4b5ad3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_F_A-T-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}